<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sydney Walkabout</string>

    <!-- Landmarks -->
    <string name="title_anzac_memorial">Anzac War Memorial</string>
    <string name="description_anzac_memorial">A physical expression of the spirit and legend of ANZAC—dedicated to remembering all Australians who have served their country in the armed forces in wartime or on peacekeeping.</string>
    <string name="title_harbour_bridge">Harbour Bridge</string>
    <string name="description_harbour_bridge">The Sydney Harbour Bridge, also affectionately known as the \'Coathanger\', was opened on March 19th 1932 by Premier Jack Lang, after six years of construction. Made of steel the bridge contains 6 million hand driven rivets. </string>
    <string name="title_opera_house">Sydney Opera House</string>
    <string name="description_opera_house">Sydney Opera House (1957 - 1973) is a masterpiece of late modern architecture. It is admired internationally and proudly treasured by the people of Australia. It was created by a young architect, Denmark\’s Jørn Utzon).</string>
    <string name="title_queen_victoria_building">Queen Victoria Building</string>
    <string name="description_queen_victoria_building">About QVB. The Queen Victoria Building, now affectionately known as the QVB, was designed by George McRae and completed in 1898. As recently as 1959 the Queen Victoria Building was threatened with demolition.</string>
    <string name="title_st_marys">St. Mary\'s Cathedral</string>
    <string name="description_st_marys">St Mary\'s Cathedral is the spiritual home of Sydney\'s Catholic community. It is the seat of the Archbishop of Sydney, and stands on the site of the first Catholic Chapel in Australia.</string>

    <!-- Beaches -->
    <string name="title_bondi">Bondi Beach</string>
    <string name="description_bondi">Bondi Beach is a popular beach and the name of the surrounding suburb in Sydney, New South Wales. It is located 7 km (4 mi) east of the Sydney central business district.</string>
    <string name="title_clovelly">Clovelly Beach</string>
    <string name="description_clovelly">Clovelly Beach is a small beach that sits on the end of the narrow bay. The bay is popular with swimmers. The bay is home to one of the first surf lifesaving clubs in the world, Clovelly Surf Life Saving Club, which was founded in 1906.</string>
    <string name="title_coogee">Coogee Beach</string>
    <string name="description_coogee">Coogee is a delightful seaside destination for families, with a patrolled beach, swimming baths and a promenade with barbeque areas and playgrounds.</string>
    <string name="title_manly">Manly Beach</string>
    <string name="description_manly">Situated between a tranquil inner-harbour beach on one side and a popular surf beach on the other, Manly combines a laid-back beachside attitude with sophisticated dining and shopping.</string>
    <string name="title_palm_beach">Palm Beach Beach</string>
    <string name="description_palm_beach">Found just over an hour’s drive from the centre of Sydney, Palm Beach is home to the city\’s most northerly stretch of sand.</string>

    <!-- Things To Do -->
    <string name="title_botanic_gardens">Royal Botanic Gardens</string>
    <string name="description_botanic_gardens">The Royal Botanic Garden Sydney is a major botanical garden located in the heart of Sydney, Australia. Opened in 1816, the garden is the oldest scientific institution in Australia and one of the most important historic botanical institutions in the world.</string>
    <string name="title_hyde_park">Hyde Park</string>
    <string name="description_hyde_park">Hyde Park, the oldest public parkland in Australia, is a 16.2-hectare (40-acre) park in the central business district of Sydney. It is famed for its magnificent fig tree lined avenues.</string>
    <string name="title_luna_park">Luna Park</string>
    <string name="description_luna_park">Visit Luna Park Sydney to catch a concert at the Big Top, eat classy cuisine at The Deck or take in the million dollar views as you ride the Ferris Wheel, as folks have been doing since 1935.</string>
    <string name="title_ocean_pool">Ocean Pool</string>
    <string name="description_ocean_pool">Ocean pools are an important feature of the Australian coastline particularly in New South Wales. Ocean pools or ocean baths are defined as public seawater pools sited on a rocky surf coast, so that waves can wash into the pool.</string>
    <string name="title_taronga_zoo">Taronga Zoo</string>
    <string name="description_taronga_zoo">Taronga Zoo is Australia\'s leading zoological park, featuring a comprehensive collection of both native and exotic species.</string>
    
    <!-- Where To Eat -->
    <string name="title_auburn">Auburn</string>
    <string name="description_auburn">If you like the sound of spicy lamb shish kebabs toasted over charcoal, visit Gozde or any of the dozen kebab joints in the Turkish enclave of Auburn.</string>
    <string name="title_cabramatta">Cabramatta</string>
    <string name="description_cabramatta">For Vietnamese spring rolls or beef pho (broth with noodles), visit Cabramatta\'s John Street.</string>
    <string name="title_chinatown">Chinatown</string>
    <string name="description_chinatown">Crispy Asian-style barbecued food can be found in Chinatown, where Dae Jang Kum Korean, Nagoya Yakiniku Japanese and Genghis Khan Mongolian have perfected the art of grilling duck, fish and meats.</string>
    <string name="title_newtown">Newtown</string>
    <string name="description_newtown">The eclectic restaurants, bars and cafes that run the length of Newtown\’s King street and up to Enmore Road make for a vibrant food scene.</string>
    <string name="title_surry_hills">Surry Hills</string>
    <string name="description_surry_hills">the Lebanese restaurants of Surry Hills\’ Cleveland Street and Lakemba are hard to beat.</string>

    <!-- Tab Headings -->
    <string name="tab_landmarks">Landmarks</string>
    <string name="tab_beaches">Beaches</string>
    <string name="tab_things_to_do">Things To Do</string>
    <string name="tab_where_to_eat">Where To Eat</string>
</resources>
